const data = [
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1ea2df",
        "question": "Which of these denotes a single line comment in Go?",
        "options": [
            "//",
            "<!-- -->",
            "/* */",
            "#"
        ],
        "answer": "//",
        "category": "golang",
        "qid": "golang000720",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.223Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.223Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976035c848f0cd9f1eb0bc",
        "question": "Who invented the electric light bulb?",
        "options": [
            "Thomas Edison",
            "Benjamin Franklin",
            "Albert Einstein",
            "Nikola Tesla"
        ],
        "answer": "Thomas Edison",
        "category": "node",
        "qid": "node000411",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.232Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.232Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9bfe",
        "question": "What should be the return type of a function in C++ when it doesn’t return a value and doesn’t take any arguments?",
        "options": [
            "int",
            "void",
            "char",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "void",
        "category": "cpp",
        "qid": "cpp001101",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.218Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.218Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976035c848f0cd9f1eb0d2",
        "question": "What is the use of require() function in node.js?",
        "options": [
            "It is used to load and cache JavaScript modules",
            "It is used to run JavaScript code",
            "It is used to create server",
            "It is used to create HTML pages"
        ],
        "answer": "It is used to load and cache JavaScript modules",
        "category": "node",
        "qid": "node000433",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.232Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.232Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1ea2f0",
        "question": "What is the format for a multi-line comment in Go?",
        "options": [
            "//...",
            "/*...*/",
            "--...--",
            "#...#"
        ],
        "answer": "/*...*/",
        "category": "golang",
        "qid": "golang000737",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.223Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.223Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976035c848f0cd9f1eb0c3",
        "question": "What is the standard unit of distance in the Metric System?",
        "options": [
            "Milligram",
            "Pound",
            "Inch",
            "Meter"
        ],
        "answer": "Meter",
        "category": "node",
        "qid": "node000418",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.232Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.232Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e98a4",
        "question": "In C++, what is the use of dynamic_cast?",
        "options": [
            "Is used for performing runtime type checking",
            "Casting static variables",
            "Casting input and output",
            "There is no such thing in C++"
        ],
        "answer": "Is used for performing runtime type checking",
        "category": "cpp",
        "qid": "cpp000243",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.213Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.213Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1ea2f1",
        "question": "What is the function used to format a string without printing it in Go?",
        "options": [
            "fmt.Sprint",
            "fmt.Print",
            "fmt.Fprint",
            "fmt.Println"
        ],
        "answer": "fmt.Sprint",
        "category": "golang",
        "qid": "golang000738",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.223Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.223Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9543",
        "question": "Who developed the C programming language?",
        "options": [
            "Dennis Ritchie",
            "James Gosling",
            "Bjarne Stroustrup",
            "Guido van Rossum"
        ],
        "answer": "Dennis Ritchie",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000003",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9545",
        "question": "What is the term for the process of finding errors and fixing them in a program?",
        "options": [
            "Compiling",
            "Executing",
            "Debugging",
            "Checking"
        ],
        "answer": "Debugging",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000005",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9541",
        "question": "How can a constant be defined in C?",
        "options": [
            "Using = operator",
            "Using const keyword",
            "Using constant keyword",
            "Using define keyword"
        ],
        "answer": "Using const keyword",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000001",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.208Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.208Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9551",
        "question": "Which header file is necessary for using functions like malloc(), calloc() and free()?",
        "options": [
            "'conio.h'",
            "'stdio.h'",
            "'stdlib.h'",
            "'dos.h'"
        ],
        "answer": "'stdlib.h'",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000017",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9561",
        "question": "What is the maximum length of an identifier in C?",
        "options": [
            "32 characters",
            "63 characters",
            "128 characters",
            "There is no limit"
        ],
        "answer": "63 characters",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000033",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9581",
        "question": "What is the purpose of a header file in C?",
        "options": [
            "To declare functions",
            "To include libraries",
            "To define constants",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000065",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e95c2",
        "question": "What is the maximum number of dimensions an array in C may have?",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "As many as your computer's memory will allow"
        ],
        "answer": "As many as your computer's memory will allow",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000130",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.209Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9641",
        "question": "What does the following statement declare?\nchar *p[10];",
        "options": [
            "Array of 10 pointers to char",
            "Pointer to an array of 10 chars",
            "Array of 10 chars",
            "Pointer to array of strings"
        ],
        "answer": "Array of 10 pointers to char",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000257",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.210Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.210Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9742",
        "question": "A C pointer is:",
        "options": [
            "A memory address",
            "A data type",
            "A binary number",
            "A C keyword"
        ],
        "answer": "A memory address",
        "category": "c",
        "qid": "c000514",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.211Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.211Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9949",
        "question": "Which C++ library provides functions to manipulate date and time?",
        "options": [
            "<utility>",
            "<date>",
            "<calendar>",
            "<chrono>"
        ],
        "answer": "<chrono>",
        "category": "cpp",
        "qid": "cpp000408",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.214Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.214Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1e9d32",
        "question": "How to select all <p> elements inside <div> elements?",
        "options": [
            "div p",
            "div > p",
            "div + p",
            "div . p"
        ],
        "answer": "div p",
        "category": "css",
        "qid": "css000297",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.219Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.219Z"
    },
    {
        "_id": "65976034c848f0cd9f1ea568",
        "question": "Where is the correct place to insert a JavaScript in an HTML document?",
        "options": [
            "<body> section",
            "<head> section",
            "Both the <head> section and the <body> section are correct",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Both the <head> section and the <body> section are correct",
        "category": "html",
        "qid": "html000281",
        "createdAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.225Z",
        "updatedAt": "2024-01-05T01:49:41.225Z"
    }
]

export default data;